RANI POTLA

CONTACT

Phone: 9490267713

Email: ranirp6404@gmail.com

Address: 509 C Sector4,

Ukkunagaram,

Visakhapatan

EDUCATION

2015 - 2019

University College of Engineering, Kakinada

Mechanical Engineering

SKILLS

- Video Labelling (Humanloop)
- CSS
- HTML
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- Illustration
- · Logo Designing

PERSONAL PROFILE

To land a challenging job in a reputable company so I may broaden my knowledge, skills, and learnings. Obtain a responsible career path that will allow me to make the most of my experience while significantly contributing to the organization's growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2022 - Present

Andhra Pradesh Government

Amenities Secretary

- Creating awareness to the citizens about all the government schemes and make them to make good use of the schemes.
- · Taking care of non burning street lights.
- Collecting of water tax and taking care of the process to new water connection to the citizens in need of it.
- Sending the applications regarding new roads and drains needed by the citizens to the higher officials and taking care till the construction and citizen satisfaction
- Maintaining proper records of all the above tasks both hard copy and soft copy of excels well prepared

2021-2022

NVIDIA

Process Executive

- Validating, Video Labelling for Autonomous cars.
- Synchronizing recorded video files to master database, annotation of images.

HOBBIES

- Digital Art
- Character Designing
- Solving Rubik's Cube

Finding Road signs, Lane, Lights, Pedestrians, Vehicles,
Infrastructure in video sequences of a camera mounted on the front of a car.

PROJECTS

Personal Projects

- Created a clone of BROCHILL website home page using HTML and CSS.
- Created Forms with form validations using HTML, CSS and JavaScript .
- Working on creating a clone of OYO website.
- Working on creating a personal website using ReactJS